{
    "subject": "resource/Henry_Cuellar",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Laredo,_Texas",
    "human_readable": "Henry Cuellar was born in Laredo, Texas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.921330451965332,
            "question": "Where was Henry Cuellar born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8983088135719299,
            "question": "Is Henry Cuellar from Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7476311326026917,
            "question": "What city is associated with Henry Cuellar's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7191675305366516,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Henry Cuellar's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6833361983299255,
            "question": "Henry Cuellar's birth city is in which region of the US?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6781553030014038,
            "question": "What is the full name of Henry Cuellar's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6666890382766724,
            "question": "Where was Henry Cuellar raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47483205795288086,
            "question": "What state is Laredo located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29825109243392944,
            "question": "What US state is known for Laredo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23137551546096802,
            "question": "Is Laredo a city in the United States?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Henry Cuellar was born in Laredo, Texas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3353_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What US state is known for Laredo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3353_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is Laredo located in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3353_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Henry Cuellar raised?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3353_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3353_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3353_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3353_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3353_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3353_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3353_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3353_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3353_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3353_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3353_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide consistent information that Henry Cuellar was indeed born in Laredo, Texas. This information is mentioned in files 12.txt, 15.txt, 22.txt, and others."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple instances confirming that Henry Cuellar was born in Laredo, Texas. Therefore, the statement \"Henry Cuellar was born in Laredo, Texas\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}